import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map> questionBank = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': '1. Who is current Prime Minister of India?',
    'A': 'Narendra Modi',
    'B': 'Amit Shah',
    'C': 'Rahul Gandhi',
    'D': 'Manmohan Singh',
    'answer': 'A',
    'bgColor': Colors.red,
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': '2. What is the captial of India?',
    'A': 'Gujarat',
    'B': 'Goa',
    'C': 'Delhi',
    'D': 'Madhya Pradesh',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.amber,
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question': '3. Which team won the most cups in IPL?',
    'A': 'Mumbai Indians',
    'B': 'Chennai Super Kings',
    'C': 'RCB',
    'D': 'KKR',
    'answer': 'A',
    'bgColor': Colors.indigoAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question': '4. Which is the first movie of Marvel Cinematic Universe?',
    'A': 'Thor',
    'B': 'Captain America',
    'C': 'Iron Man',
    'D': 'Ant Man',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.blue,
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question': "5. What is the name of Wolverine's Character?",
    'A': 'Logan',
    'B': 'Charles x Xavier',
    'C': 'Erik Leishner',
    'D': 'James McAvoy',
    'answer': 'A',
    'bgColor': Colors.green,
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question': "6. On ________ is Independence Day of India",
    'A': '15 August',
    'B': '2 October',
    'C': '26 January',
    'D': 'None of the Above',
    'answer': 'A',
    'bgColor': Colors.yellowAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question': "7. Which is World's Highest Grossing Movie? ",
    'A': 'Endgame',
    'B': 'Titanic',
    'C': 'Avatar',
    'D': 'No Way Home',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.indigoAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question': "8. There are total ___ Planets in Solar System ",
    'A': '9',
    'B': '7',
    'C': '8',
    'D': '11',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.pink,
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'question': "9. In Which year Titanic Ship Sink? ",
    'A': '1910',
    'B': '1921',
    'C': '1991',
    'D': '1912',
    'answer': 'D',
    'bgColor': Colors.lightBlue,
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'question': "10. How many districts are there in Gujarat? ",
    'A': '37',
    'B': '27',
    'C': '33',
    'D': '31',
    'answer': 'C',
    'bgColor': Colors.deepPurpleAccent,
  },
];
